The Guide to the Hiteman Leather Company records, 1898-1968
Hiteman Leather Company records, 1898-1968
- "Raw Materials": Hide Records, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 6)
- "R": Price lists, correspondence, orders, enclosures, 2 leather samples, 1964-1965 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- "S": Correspondence, leather reports, invoices, orders, 1964-1965 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- "Tanners' Council of America - Past Due Accounts": Reports, 1964-1965 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- "Tanners' Council Lab": Correspondence, lab reports, reporting forms, 1964-1965 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- "Tanners' Council of America Trade Survey Bureau": Weekly production reports, 1964-1965 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- "Tanners' Council News": Newsletters, 1964-1965 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- "Tanners' Council of America": Correspondence, form letters, reports, annual meeting proceedings, news bulletin, 1964-1965 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- "Marianne Tater": Correspondence, color and texture report, news-ads, 1964-1965 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- "Time Studies": Hourly rate schedules, reports, 1963-1965 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- "T": Invoices, orders, correspondence, enclosures, 1964-1965 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- "Town and Country": Orders, invoices, correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- "United States Shoe Corp.": Invoices, orders, correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- "U": Correspondence, invoices, leather samples, 1964-1965 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- "V": Correspondence and enclosures re swer system and treatment, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- "Water Pollution": Correspondence, reports, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 21)
- "A.L. Webster": Hide market reports, 1964-1965 (Box 20, Folder 22)
- "Bub Wheeler's folder": Correspondence, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 23)
- Untitled: Credit memos, shipping copies, adding machine tapes, notes, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 24)
- "W": Correspondence, invoices, orders, reports, 1964-1965 (Box 20, Folder 25)
- "X-Y-Z": Orders, correspondence, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 26)
- "Remittances": Receipted bills and invoices, notes, copy receipts, 1964-1965 (Box 20, Folder 27)
- "J. G. Forte": Invoices, contracts re purchase of skins, 1965-1968 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- "H": Orders, invoices, contracts re hides, 1964-1968 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- "Emil Kohn": Invoices, contracts, shipping bills re sale of hides, 1964-1968 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- "E. Landsberg": Invoices re buying of hides, 1963-1968 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- "Martin & Stewart": Contracts, invoices, shipping bills re buying of hides, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- "M & F Hide Co.": Invoices and other business papers re buying hides, 1963-1968 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- "Michigan Hide Co.": Accounts on sale of hides, 1963-1968 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- "N": 2 Hides Companys - accounts of sale of hides to Hiteman's, 1966-1967 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- "O": Hide sale records, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- "P": Records re buying hides, 1963-1968 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- "Pd. skin invoices for the month": Bills, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- "Ralph Packing": Contracts, bills, receipts, shipping information re buying of hides, 1963-1967 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- "St. Louis Hide": Summary of sales, invoices, constructs, control sheets for hides, 1965-1966 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- "F. Schrowee": Correspondence, bills, receiving sheets, etc. re hides, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- "A. Sklut": Invoices, correspondence, receiving sheets re hides, 1964-1965 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- "Skorinpex": Correspondence, insurance forms, bills of lading, contract, invoice re hides (imported), 1966 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- "Sokalner and Senott": Accounts re buying hides, 1964-1966 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- "Standard": Account re hides, trucking form, receiving sheets, etc., 1963 (Box 21, Folder 18)
- "Swift": Contract, receiving sheet and summary of skins bought, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 19)
- "United Dress Beef": Papers re summary of skins received, 1963-1965 (Box 21, Folder 20)
- "Utica Freezer": Warehouse receipts, inspection reports, 1965- (Box 21, Folder 21)
- "E. & S. Waterbury": Invoices, receiving sheets, storage receipts and summary of skins received, 1963-1964 (Box 21, Folder 22)
- "West Chester Hide": Receipts and summaries of skins received, 1967-1968 (Box 21, Folder 23)
- "Wolverine": Receipts and summaries of skins received, 1963-1968 (Box 21, Folder 24)
- "Eden & Strass": Shipping records, invoices, summaries of hides bought and sold, 1958-1959 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- "Feldman Trading Corp. Comm. Paid": Contracts, bills, receiving notices, summaries, 1961-1962 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- "Kaufmann Trading Co.": Bills, contracts, 1958-1959 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- "Landsbery Comm. Paid": Bills, receiving slips, 1961-1962 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- "Martin & Stewart Limited": Bills, contracts, receiving slips, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- "Mohawk Valley Wool Co.": Bills, summary of sales, 1959-1961 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- "Philadelphia Hide Corporation": Bills, summaries, receiving slips, 1958-1962 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- "Ralph Packing Comm. Paid": Bills, summaries of sales, 1959-1960 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- "Sukalner Serott Hide Corp. Comm. Paid": Invoices, sales summary, receiving slips, insurance certificate, 1959-1962 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- "The Tupman Thurlow Co., Inc.": Bills, shipping instructions, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- "Willo Packing Comm. Paid": Sales material for hides, 1960-1961 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- "Wolverine _ide Co.": Bills, correspondence, receiving slips on sale of hides, 1959-1962 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- "Nick Beucher": Hide sales and shipping records, 1963-1968 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- "Branford Comm. Packers": Hide lot sales and shipping records, 1964-1967 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- "Chester Packing Co.": Hide sales by lots, packing and shipping records, invoices, 1963-1968 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- "Eden & Strass": Hide sales records, 1963-1967 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- "Estra Trading": Bills and comm. receipts, 1964-1968 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- "E": Hide and skin companies invoices, shipping notices, 1965-1967 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- "Feldman Trading": Bills on incoming hides, 1963-1968 (Box 22, Folder 19)
- "Operations Reports 7/1/56 through [6/68]": Reports on hides, skins and leathers; most with adding machine tapes and handwritten figures, 1962-1968 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- "Sorting Room Production": Figures on types of leather and numbers, 1961-1963 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- "Sorting Room Production": Figures, 1963-1965 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- "Production": Figures, 1965-1967 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- "Hiteman Leather Co. Sorting Room Production": Loose leaf notebook; production figures, 1947-1952 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- "A": Copies of correspondence, 1916-1918 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- "B": Copies of correspondence, 1916-1918 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- "C": Copies of correspondence, 1916-1918 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- "D": Copies of correspondence, 1916-1918 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- "E-F": Copies of correspondence, 1916-1918 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- "G": Copies of correspondence, 1917-1918 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- "H-1": Copies of correspondence, 1917-1918 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- "H-2": Copies of correspondence, 1917-1918 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- "H-3": Copies of correspondence, 1918 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- "H-4": Copies of correspondence, 1917-1918 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- "H-5": Copies of correspondence, 1917 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- "H-6": Copies of correspondence, 1916-1917 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- "I-J-K": Copies of correspondence, 1916-1918 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- "A": Incoming correspondence, 1917 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- "B": Incoming correspondence, 1917 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- "C": Incoming correspondence, enclosures, 1917 (Box 24, Folder 16)
- "D": Correspondence, enclosures, sales reports, 1917 (Box 24, Folder 17)
- "E-F": Correspondence; market and sales, reports, 1916-1917 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- "G": Incoming correspondence, 1917 (Box 24, Folder 19)
- "H-1": Incoming correspondence, 1917 (Box 24, Folder 20)
- "H-2": Incoming correspondence, bills, 1917 (Box 24, Folder 21)
- "I-J": Incoming correspondence, 1917 (Box 24, Folder 22)
- "K": Incoming correspondence, 1917 (Box 24, Folder 23)
- "Li-Ly": Incoming correspondence, 1919 (Box 24, Folder 24)
- "Ma-Mc": Correspondence, invoices, 1919 (Box 24, Folder 25)
- "Me-Mi": Correspondence, shipping memos, 1919 (Box 24, Folder 26)
- "Mo": Incoming correspondence, 1919 (Box 24, Folder 27)
- "N": Incoming correspondence, orders, 1919 (Box 24, Folder 28)
- "O-Pa-Ph": Correspondence, bill of lading, price list, 1919 (Box 24, Folder 29)
- "Pi-Py": Correspondence, list of calf skin offerings, 1919 (Box 24, Folder 30)
- "Ra-Ri": Correspondence, 1919 (Box 24, Folder 31)
- "Ro-Ry": Correspondence, bills, 1919 (Box 24, Folder 32)
- "Sa-Sd": Correspondence, 1919 (Box 24, Folder 33)
- "Se-Sl": Correspondence, orders, 1919 (Box 24, Folder 34)
- "Sn-Sr": Correspondence, orders, acknowledgements, 1919 (Box 24, Folder 35)
- "St-Sz": Sales memorandum, correspondence, 1919 (Box 24, Folder 36)
- "T": Correspondence, acknowledgement of orders, 1919 (Box 24, Folder 37)
- "U-V": Correspondence, 1919 (Box 24, Folder 38)
- "W": Correspondence, 1919 (Box 24, Folder 39)
- "C": Copies of outgoing correspondence, 1918-1919 (Box 24, Folder 40)
- "D": Correspondence copies, 1918 (Box 24, Folder 41)
- "G": Correspondence, 1918-1919 (Box 24, Folder 42)
- "H": Bills, correspondence, 1918-1920 (Box 24, Folder 43)
- "St-Sz": Skin offerings, correspondence, 1920 (Box 24, Folder 44)
- "H": Receipted bills, 1920-1921 (Box 24, Folder 45)
- "He-Hn": Correspondence, reports of calf offerings, 1920-1921 (Box 24, Folder 46)
- "He-Hn": Handwritten letters from W.E. Hiteman, telegrams, other correspondence, 1920-1921 (Box 24, Folder 47)
- "Ho-Hy": Copies of outgoing correspondence, bills, 1920-1921 (Box 24, Folder 48)
- Untitled: Production records of various departments; inventory, formulas, etc., 1925-1939 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- "Tanners Council of America Sept. 1938": Form letters, correspondence, reports, bulletins (Box 25, Folder 2)
- "Tupper, Inc.": Correspondence, accounts, orders, 1938-1939 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- "T": Correspondence, form letters, leather sample, 1938-1939 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- "United Eastern Coal Sales Corporation": Correspondence, orders, 1938-1939 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- "U": Correspondence, speech, bulletin, annual report, 1938-1939 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- "V": Correspondence, 1938-1939 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- "A. L. Webster & Co. May 1939": Correspondence, reports (Box 25, Folder 8)
- "A. L. Webster & Co. April 1939": Correspondence, reports (Box 25, Folder 9)
- "A. L. Webster & Co. March 1939": Correspondence, reports (Box 25, Folder 10)
- "A. L. Webster & Co. February 1939": Correspondence, reports (Box 25, Folder 11)
- "A. L. Webster & Co. January 1939": Correspondence, reports (Box 25, Folder 12)
- "A. L. Webster & Co. December 1938": Correspondence, reports (Box 25, Folder 13)
- "A. L. Webster & Co. November 1938": Correspondence, reports (Box 25, Folder 14)
- "A. L. Webster & Co. October 1938": Correspondence, reports (Box 25, Folder 15)
- "A. L. Webster & Co. September 1938": Correspondence (Box 25, Folder 16)
- "W": Correspondence, accounts, reports, orders, credit memos, leather sample, bills, advertising pamphlet, 1938-1939 (Box 25, Folder 17)
- "X-Y-Z": Correspondence, orders, leather sample, 1938-1939 (Box 25, Folder 18)
- "Hiteman Leather Co., Inc.": Correspondence, notes, clipping, 1939-1940 (Box 25, Folder 19)
- "Hiteman Leather Co., Inc.": Notes, 1940 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- "Hiteman Leather Co., Inc.": Correspondence, 1943-1944 (Box 25, Folder 21)
- "H": Correspondence, enclosures, reports, 1943-1944 (Box 25, Folder 22)
- "Hiteman Leather Co., Inc.": Correspondence, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 23)
- "H": Correspondence, enclosures, advertising layout suggestions, 1944-1945 (Box 25, Folder 24)
- "H": Correspondence and enclosures, 1945 (Box 25, Folder 25)
- "Hiteman Leather Co., Inc.": Notices, 1946-1947 (Box 25, Folder 26)
- "A": Correspondence, printed matter, 1947-1948 (Box 25, Folder 27)
- "Aulson Tanning Machinery Co." (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence, Sept. 16, 1947 to Mar. 10, 1948
    Orders for leather working machinery and parts; H. L. Tracey Ralph Toye; Hiteman Leather Co. Aulson Tanning Machinery Co.
- "Matt Amrose" (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, Sept. 10, 1947 to Mar. 23, 1948
    Matt Amrose George Hiteman
    Matt Amrose Hiteman Leather Co.
- "H": Correspondence, advertisements, 1947-1948 (Box 25, Folder 30)
- "Hide Sheets": Inventory - skins in hair, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 31)
- "Record": Leather samples and formulas for colors; chemical analysis, 1928-1929 (Box 25, Folder 32)
- "Charles K. Hardenburg" (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Chemical analysis of drying processes; beamhouse process, tanning process, finishing formula
- Untitled: Chemical and finishing formulas, correspondence, 1948-1957 (Box 25, Folder 34)
- Untitled: Tanning formulas and experiments, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 35)
- "Shrunken Grain": Formulas for processing, 1953-1955 (Box 25, Folder 36)
- "Ledger": Receipted bills, 1888-1889 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- "Daybook": Daily financial transactions, 1890-1892 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- "Journal": Daily statements on number, value and locations of skins, 1907-1921 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- "Journal": Record of skin lots bought and disposition, 1929-1934 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- "Journal": Record of skin lots and enclosures, 1934-1941 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- "Journal": Record of skin lots and enclosures, 1942-1950 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- "Time Book": Employees time records, 1929-1931 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Untitled: Wash, pickle, and tanning information, 1948 and undated (Box 27, Folder 2)
- "Experimental Formulas": Cost records processing information, industry stock figures, 1932-1941 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- [Formulas]: Formulas - correspondence re, 1909-1947 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Untitled: Patent specifications; soaking processes, drying process, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 5)
- "Inventory Hiteman Leather Co.": Yearly inventory sheets, 1921-1947 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Untitled: Piecework schedule, 1938-1951 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- "Soak Book November 1965 September 1966": Record of soaking raw material, 1965-1966 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- "Retirements": Machinery retirements, transfer schedules, deduction schedules, 1961-1964 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- "Hiteman Leather Co. Insurance summary report": Report of appraisal for fire insurance, 1962-1966 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- "Journal": Daily transactions, 1922-1924 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- "Cash Received - Feb. 1, 1922-June 29, 1925": Listing, checks and cash received, 1922-1925 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- "Cash Paid - July 5, 1922-January 31, 1924: Checks and cash paid, 1922-1924 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- "Cash Paid - February 1, 1924-May 29, 1925": Checks and cash paid, 1924-1925 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- "Skin Book - July 1932-April 1935": Record of skins received and processed, 1932-1935 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- "Skin Book - June 1940-March 1943": Record of skins processed, 1940-1943 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- "[-ak Bo-] Jan 195_ to Dec. 195_": Record of skins received and processed, 1954 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- "Trial Balance": Summary of business by weeks, 1891-1895 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- "Trial Balance": Weekly business summaries, 1895-1906 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- "Trial Balance": Weekly summary of business transacted - loose papers at back, 1919-1948 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- "Journal": Record of skins received and processed, 1951-1958 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- "Financial Statements - 'Quarterly' ": Statements of assets and liabilities, 1953-1961 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- "Hiteman Leather Co. Day Book": Daily financial transactions, 1922-1962 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- "Hiteman Leather Co. Miscellaneous sales": Sales receipts and monthly summary, 1963-1967 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- "Hiteman Leather Co. 'Sales' ": Sales and returns separated by [salesmen's names]?, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- "Hiteman Leather Company - Sales": Sales reports and returns, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- "Hiteman Leather Co. - Price Lists": Price lists for types of leather; shipping information, 1966-1968 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- "Hiteman Leather Co. 'Sorting Room Production - Front' ": Production figures, 1952-1956 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- "Ledger": Daily business transactions, 1891-1903 (Bound Volumes, Volume 1)
- "Checks and Cash Paid - June 1, 1925 to December 31, 1927": Checks and cash paid out, 1925-1927 (Volume 2)
- "Cash Payments January 8, 1954 to December 31, 1964": Outgoing payments (Volume 3)
- "Hiteman Leather Company... Cash Receipts July 1954 to ----": Outgoing payments, 1954-1965 (Volume 4)